# VENU K

### ANALYST

+919740173915

venukodandaram@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/venukodandaram-b77982ba/

## PROFILE SUMMARY

I graduated as Electronics and Communication Engineer from VTU, Belgavi in 2019. But my passion is to develop my career in Data Science, Machine Learning and Deep Learning technology.

Worked as Data Science intern and had a good exposure on deep learning at Flux Auto, from December 2019 to December 2020. Since December 2020, I am working in Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited as Analyst.

### SKILLS

SQL Informatica POSTMAN Data Science

SAP HANA CHS Argus Safety Machine Learning

Crystal Reports ETL Python Deep Learning

#### EDUCATION

B.E (Electronics and Comunication Engineering)

2016 - 2019

Dayananda Sagar Academy Of Technology and Management, Bangalore

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Analyst Dec, 2020 - Present

### Deloiite, Bangalore

- Understood the client requirement (USA, Europe and Japan) and creating the SQL quires for it.
- Crystal reports complete end-to-end development.
- Developed the Informatica mappings for ETL.
- Implemented AAL (Advance Auto Labelling) Technique in Argus Safety as requested by Client.
- Involved in Production Environment configuration and deployment.

Data Science Intern Dec, 2019 - Dec, 2020

# Flux Auto, Bangalore

- Worked with US and Europe client on Image and Lidar data processing.
- Data Annotation using the VGG tool and online cloud tool on U.S.A and Indian Data.
- Created deep learning models in terms of varying parameters, learning rates, epochs, and Accuracy for image classification and detection.
- Worked on Lidar data and also PCDs using unity hub.

### CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Data Scientist by IABAC
- Neural Networks by DeepLearning.AI (Coursera)
- Machine Learning by Stanford University (Coursera)
- Deep Learning by DeepLearning.Al (Coursera)
- Data Analysis with python by Jovian.
- Personality Development training by CIL, DSI.
- RTL Design Intern at Innovations Labs, DSU.

# ACHEIVEMENTS/AWARDS

# **EL Asia 2019 International Exhibition**

Presented our academic project in this International Exhibition in 2019.

# National Conference, DSATM, Bangalore

Presented technical papers on "Wireless Monitoring Controller for Agriculture" in National Conference on Convergence of Science, Technology and Management(NCCSTM-2019).

### Flux Auto, Bangalore

Successfully delivered more than 100 GB of data annotation, data processing and data quality upon this received an appreciation (great performer) by a client in 2020.

#### **Deloitte**

Star Performer Award in 2021

#### **Deloitte**

**Spot Award in 2022**